Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: Congressional Activities, 1995-2012
  - Series 6: Correspondence, 2006-2012
    - Subseries 1: Acknowledgement and Invitations, 2007-2012
      - Requests, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Requests (1 of 3), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Requests (2 of 3), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Requests (3 of 3), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Requests, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Subseries 2: Letters from other officials, 2006-2012
      This subseries contains letters from a variety of government officials as well as Giffords outgoing correspondence to other officials. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - Bennett, Ken, 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Boehner, John, January 6, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Brewer, Janice, March 20, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - General, 2006-2012 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Giffords Outgoing, 2007-2010 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Gore, Al, April 6, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - International, 2007-2011 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Members of Congress, 2006-2011 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Military, 2007-2012 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Napolitano, Janet, December 10, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Pelosi, Nancy, 2007-2011 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Walkup, Robert, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Subseries 3: Constituent Mail, 2007-2012
      This subseries contains correspondence from constituents organized by year and month as well as form letters sent from constituents on a variety of issues, primarily legislation. Form letters were sampled. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - Form letters (1 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Form letters (2 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Form letters (3 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Form letters (4 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Form letters (5 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Form letters (6 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Form letters (7 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Form letters (8 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Form letters (9 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Form letters (10 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Form letters (11 of 11), 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - General, 2007-2010 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - General (1 of 2), January, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 2), January, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - General (1 of 2), February, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - General (2 of 2), February, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 3), March, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 3), March, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - General (3 of 3), March, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - General (1 of 3), April, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - General (2 of 3), April, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - General (3 of 3), April, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - General (1 of 2), May, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - General (2 of 2), May, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - General (1 of 3), June, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - General (2 of 3), June, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - General (3 of 3), June, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 2), July, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 2), July, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - General (1 of 3), August, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - General (2 of 3), August, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - General (3 of 3), August, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - General (1 of 3), September, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - General (2 of 3), September, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - General (3 of 3), September, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - General (1 of 2), October, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - General (2 of 2), October, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - General (1 of 2), November, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - General (2 of 2), November, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - General, December, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 2), 2012 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 2), 2012 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Opinion Ballot, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Subseries 4: Form Letters, 2009-2010
      This subseries contains form letter responses from Giffords covering a wide array of topics. It is arranged alphabetically by topic.
      - Abortion/Health Insurance Reform, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Administration, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Agriculture, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Animals, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Budget, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Business, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Defense, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Education, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Energy, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Environment, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Family, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Finance, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Foreign Affairs, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Government, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Health, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Housing, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Immigration, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Judiciary, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Labor, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - LGBT, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Medicare/Medicaid, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Natives, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Regulation, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Science, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Social Security, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Taxes, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Trade, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Transportation, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Veterans, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Women, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Series 7: Office Files, 2006-2011
    This series contains schedules, event and travel itineraries and materials related to the management of Giffords’ office.
    - Subseries 1: Schedules, 2009-2010
      This subseries contains schedules and schedule analyses by topic. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - District of Columbia Calendar breakdown by topic (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - District of Columbia Calendar breakdown by topic (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - District of Columbia schedule, 2009-2010 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Subseries 2: Travel, 2007-2009
      This subseries contains correspondence and itineraries related to Giffords’ travel primarily for congressional delegations. It is arranged chronologically.
      - Congressional delegation Kyl- Kuwait, Iraq, Israel, February 16, 2007-February 20, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Congressional delegation Israel, Sponsored by The American Israel Education Foundation, August 12, 2007-August 18, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Iraq, Kuwait (1 of 2), November 2, 2007-November 5, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Iraq, Kuwait (2 of 2), November 2, 2007-November 5, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Afghanistan, Pakistan, April 24, 2008-April 29, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- United Kingdom, Afghanistan, Pakistan, April 24, 2008-April 29, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Israel, Lebanon, Syria, Kuwait, Iraq, Belgium (1 of 2), January 28, 2009-February 3, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Israel, Lebanon, Syria, Kuwait, Iraq, Belgium (2 of 2), January 28, 2009-February 3, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Burkina Faso, Democratic Republic of Congo, Kenya, Yemen, Egypt, Morocco (1 of 5), April 14, 2009-April 21, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Burkina Faso, Democratic Republic of Congo, Kenya, Yemen, Egypt, Morocco (2 of 5), April 14, 2009-April 21, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Burkina Faso, Democratic Republic of Congo, Kenya, Yemen, Egypt, Morocco (3 of 5), April 14, 2009-April 21, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Burkina Faso, Democratic Republic of Congo, Kenya, Yemen, Egypt, Morocco (4 of 5), April 14, 2009-April 21, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Congressional delegation Smith- Burkina Faso, Democratic Republic of Congo, Kenya, Yemen, Egypt, Morocco (5 of 5), April 14, 2009-April 21, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Congressional delegation Pelosi- Copenhagen, December 7, 2009-December 18, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Ovagadougou, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Subseries 3: Events, 2007-2011
      This subseries contains correspondence and schedules related to events that Giffords attended. It is arranged chronologically.
      - National Democratic Jewish Council 110th Congress Swearing-In Reception, January 4, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Governor's Tribal Summit on Education and Growth, February 15, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Veterans Advisory Council (1 of 2), February 23, 2007-June 7, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Veterans Advisory Council (2 of 2), February 23, 2007-June 7, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Hendricks Elementary Event, March 2, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Fred G. Acosta Job Corp Center Industry Council Meeting/Luncheon, March 28, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - State of the District Luncheon, March 30, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Healthcare Roundtable, April 12, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, May 5, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - No Child Left Behind Virtual Town Hall, May 9, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Arizona Trail Federal Designation and Volunteer Awards, May 12, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - 309th Aerospace Maintenance and Regeneration Group, F-14 aircraft destruction, Davis-Monthan Air Force Base, May 19, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Congress on Your Corner - Safe Summer for Children, June 2, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Immigration Impact Roundtable, July 3, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Tucson Association of Realtors and Southern Arizona Home Builders Association, July 3, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Solar Energy Press Conference and Solarfest, July 5, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Preventing Scams that Target Seniors, July 6, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Senior and Aging Issues Advisory Council, July 6, 2007-January 11, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Medicare Forum, August 24, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Tucson Education Association, August, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Empire High School and National Aeronautics and Space Administration Video Conference, October 19, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Veterans Oral History Project, October 19, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Academic Achievement Assembly, Sahuarita High School, December 5, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Dedication, Rattlesnake Ridge Elementary, December 7, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Naval Reserve Officers' Training Corps Commissioning Ceremony, December 14, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Senior Retirement Council, 2007-2010 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Faith Community, 2007-2011 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Economic Stimulus Roundtable, January 10, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Regional College Access Center Press Conference, January 16, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Greater Sierra Vista United Veterans Council, January 24, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Mathematics Educator Appreciation Day Conference, Tucson Magnet High School, January 26, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - 27th Annual School Counselor-Administrator Symposium, February 1, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Air Force Association Appreciation Luncheon, February 22, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Read Across America, Hudlow Elementary School, March 3, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Keep the "US" in Tucson Unified School District Rally, March 10, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Dedication, David Ashcroft Center for Performing Arts, Sahuaro High School, March 16, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Veterans Conference Call, April 10, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Meeting on Green Valley Public Safety Issues, April 21, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Department of Homeland Security Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency, May 2, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, May 10, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Community Conversation on Early Childhood Education, May 20, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Drug Trafficking and Illegal Drug Sale, May 23, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Space Shuttle Discovery launch, STS-124 mission, May 31, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - LEARN Program Graduation Celebration, June 12, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - Flag Day Ceremony, Green Valley Elks Lodge, June 14, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - Veterans Issues Teleconference, June 24, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - Southern Arizona Solar Energy Development Conference, June 30, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Water Issues Town Hall, July 1, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Video Teleconference on Monitoring the Environmental Impact of Border Fencing, July 9, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Making Big Solar Work: Achievements, Challenges and Opportunities, July 29, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Report on the Economy, July, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Energy Policy Briefings, Energy Crisis Myths and Realities, August 11, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - 2008 Foreclosure Prevention Events Steering Committee, August 14, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election, August 22, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Community Initiative on Veterans' Mental Health Services, September 6, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Southern Arizona Charter Schools, September 17, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Senior Health and Wellness Forum, September 29, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Solar Power 101, October 28, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Arizona Education Association Annual Legislative Reception, December 13, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Arizona Leadership Summit on Solar Energy and Economics, January 8, 2009-January 9, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - 56th Presidential Inaugural Ceremonies, United States Capitol Building, January 20, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Refuge Student and Parent Services Advisory Council, January 28, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Financing Solar in Hard Times: A Policy Review, February 20, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Economic Recovery Forums, February, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Border Violence Summit, April 7, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Solar Energy Roundtable, April 10, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - The Future of Photovoltaic Manufacturing in the United States, April 23, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Healthcare Reform Roundtable, May 1, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, May 2, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Pima County Workforce Investment Board retreat, May 8, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Healthcare Town Hall, May 26, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Conference Call with Bankers on Foreclosure, July 14, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Recovery Act Tour, August 6, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Congressional Update, August 13, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - GI Bill Forum, August 13, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Faith Leaders Roundtable, August 31, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Health Insurance Reform, August, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Health Insurance Reform Town Hall, September 1, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Touch Point, September 10, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Drug Interdiction Strategies and Progress Briefing, September 18, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Pride Rally at Bowie Schools, September 18, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Recovery Tour, October 2, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - Amber Lights, October 4, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Proposed Rosemont Mine, October 24, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Medal Presentation Ceremony for Paul Rung, November 11, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Post-9/11 GI Bill Press Conference, November 12, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Briefing on Economic Recovery funding secured by University of Arizona, November 23, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Presentation of United States Flag to Marana Library, November 24, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Border Fence Monitoring and Mitigation Project, December 7, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Job Hunters Boot Camp, San Mateo, California, January 28, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Coyote Trail Elementary School visit for "Love of Reading" week, February 8, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Secretary of Labor Hilda Solis, February 16, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Declaration of Independence, February 21, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Mayor's Stimulus, February 22, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Senior and Aging Issues Advisory Council, March 5, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Briefing for 2011 Appropriations Requests, March, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Arizona Leadership Solar Bus Tour, April 1, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Solar Schools Act, April 1, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Community Forum on Health Insurance Reform, April 7, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Job Seekers Expo, April 17, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, April 24, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Telephone Town Hall, April 26, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Senior and Aging Issues Advisory Council, June 7, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Congressional Update at The Forum, June 12, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Let Freedom Sing 4th of July Celebration, July 4, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Statewide Symposium in Support of Military Families, July 14, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Assistant Secretary Cathy Zoi, August 18, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Predatory Lending Sunset Act, August 26, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Medal Ceremony for Archibald Jackson, September 8, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Foreclosure Prevention Workshop, September 13, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Solar Energy Roundtable, September 13, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Canyon Del Oro High School Visit with Senator Mark Udall, October 26, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - 2nd Annual Holiday Cards to the Troops, Southern Arizona Veterans Affairs Health Care System, December 18, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Solar Power 101: A Community Education Series on Solar Energy, March 24, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Border Security Tour, Malpai Ranch, March 25, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, May 7, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Captain Mark Kelly remarks to the National Press Club, Washington, D.C., June 28, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - General Services Administration Roundtable, October 26, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Giffords Traumatic Brain Injury Town Hall, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - 8th Congressional District Art Competition Awards Ceremony, ca. May, 2012 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - Talking points, F-35 Lightning II Joint Strike Fighter, undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Subseries 4: Staff Files, 2006-2011
      This subseries contains materials from Giffords’ staff members including staff memos and reports, office policies and staff retreats. Also included are Giffords’ biographies and information related to her resignation from Congress.
      - Employee handbook, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Event ideas, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 40)
      - Events, 2006-2011 (Box 41, Folder 41)
      - Giffords biographies, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - Giffords for Congress campaign issue statements, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Guestbook sign-in, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - Invitations- Mark Kelly, 2011-2012 (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Meetings, 2009-2011 (Box 41, Folder 46)
      - Memorandums (1 of 2), 2007-2011 (Box 41, Folder 47)
      - Memorandums (2 of 2), 2007-2011 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - Notebooks, 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Resignation, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Staff assignments, 2008-2011 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Staff plans, 2008-2010 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Staff retreat, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Staff retreat, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Transition plan for Congresswoman-Elect Gabrielle Giffords, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Series 8: Press Files, 2007-2011
    This series contains news clippings, franked mail, newsletters and articles written by Giffords. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Articles by Giffords, 2007-2010 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Attack Ads, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Franked mail (1 of 5), 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Franked mail (2 of 5), 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Franked mail (3 of 5), 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Franked mail (4 of 5), 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Franked mail (5 of 5), 2007-2011 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Health Care Press Kit, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - News clippings (1 of 5), 2007 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - News clippings (2 of 5), 2007 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - News clippings (3 of 5), 2007 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - News clippings (4 of 5), 2007 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - News clippings (5 of 5), 2007 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - News clippings (1 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - News clippings (2 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - News clippings (3 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - News clippings (4 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - News clippings (5 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - News clippings (6 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - News clippings (7 of 7), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - News clippings (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - News clippings (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - News clippings (1 of 3), 2010 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - News clippings (2 of 3), 2010 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - News clippings (3 of 3), 2010 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - News clippings, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - News clippings (1 of 2), 2012 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - News clippings (2 of 2), 2012 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, 2010-2011 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Web Site, 2007-2010 (Box 44 A, Folder 1)
- Subgroup II: Media Files, 2005-2012
  This subgroup contains photographs, audio visual materials and memorabilia. Some access copies of audio visual materials are available. The migrated copies of these audio visual materials were transferred from the originals in 2015.
  - Series 1: Photographic Materials, 2006-2010
    This series contains photographs of community events, congressional delegations and important figures.
    - Army Sustainability Dinner, 2009 (Box 44 A, Folder 2)
    - Bisbee Museum, undated (Box 44 A, Folder 3)
    - Brewer, Jan, 2009 (Box 44 A, Folder 4)
    - Community Development Block Grant celebration, undated (Box 44 A, Folder 5)
    - Events, unidentified, undated (Box 44 A, Folder 6)
    - Fundraiser, Wilmington, Delaware, August, 2009 (Box 44 A, Folder 7)
    - Giffords promotional shots, 2010 (Box 44 A, Folder 8)
    - Napolitano, Janet, 2008 (Box 44 A, Folder 9)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 2006-2010 (Box 44 A, Folder 10)
    - Obamas, 2009 (Box 44 A, Folder 11)
    - Rodeo parade, 2008 (Box 44 A, Folder 12)
    - Staff and Interns, 2008 (Box 44 A, Folder 13)
    - Swearing-in ceremony, 2007-2011 (Box 44 A, Folder 14)
  - Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 2005-2012
    This series contains video, audio and computer files related to Giffords’ congressional career.
    - Subseries 1: Video cassettes, 2007-2010
      This subseries contains videos of Giffords’ television appearances and floor statements. It is arranged alphabetically.